https://iexpe.org/information-library/institute-documents/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Institute of Explosives Engineers
Contact us
My AccountLog in
Search for:
MenuMy AccountLog inHomeThe Institute & Its RoleSSSGIntroducing the SSSGSSSG Documents LibraryCorporate MembershipPast Accident ReviewEducation and TrainingExplosives E&R TrustTraining & ResearchGrants & RewardsTrusteesMembershipWho Can Apply For MembershipThe Benefits of MembershipMake an Application for MembershipProfessional Registration for MembersMembers Online Resource LibraryOur Key Partners & AffiliatesGuidance for RefereesFees & SubscriptionsRenew Your Membership (2020)Information & LibraryKnowledgebaseJobsCareers & DevelopmentJobsSTEM FuturesRole ProfilesmycareerpathProfessional Registration ApplicationsCSCSVotes & NominationsIExpE MerchandiseJournals2020 Journal Awards CompetitionPast PublicationsAbout The JournalAdvertising InformationJournal Subscription RatesSubmit An ArticlePublicationsPublicationsInstitute DocumentsIExpE Brand GuidelinesInstitute BusinessArticle of ConstitutionPolicy and ProceduresCode of ConductCPD PolicyPrivacy PolicyUseful AcronymsPartners & AffiliatesPartnersEU ExcertEU Excert UKEU ExImp ProjectSSBAffiliated OrganisationsSAFEXEFEEEngineering CouncilOrganisations of InterestCogentHSEEIFNational Occupational StandardsENBCBI Explosives GroupIExpE PresidentIExpE Company MembersNews & EventsInstitute NewsIExpE Conference CentreEventsFulmination 2021Section Navigation Institute DocumentsIExpE Brand GuidelinesPolicy and ProceduresArticle of ConstitutionCode of ConductCPD PolicyPrivacy PolicyUseful Acronyms
Tweets by IExpE
Tweets by IExpE
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThe Institute of Explosives Engineers dislike websites that secretly gather their users information and sell it on to other parties.  When you are on our website any information you give is secure and will not go anywhere other than where you intended it to go.  We promise not to sell, give away or misuse your details.As a benefit of your membership we may contact you with our own marketing information from time to time.Opt-OutIf at any time you wish to withdraw consent to receipt of marketing material please contact the IExpE Admin OfficeCookie PolicyThis website uses cookies, for further information contact the IExpE Admin Office
The Sector Skills Strategy Group (SSSG)A collaborative group of organisations who provide strategic direction to sustain explosives skills.
Learn MoreCall Us01785 594136©1998 - 2020 Institute of Explosives Engineers.
HomeThe Institute & Its RoleSSSGIntroducing the SSSGSSSG Documents LibraryCorporate MembershipPast Accident Review BackEducation and TrainingExplosives E&R TrustTraining & ResearchGrants & RewardsTrustees BackMembershipWho Can Apply For MembershipThe Benefits of MembershipMake an Application for MembershipProfessional Registration for MembersMembers Online Resource LibraryOur Key Partners & AffiliatesGuidance for RefereesFees & SubscriptionsRenew Your Membership (2020) BackInformation & LibraryKnowledgebaseJobsCareers & DevelopmentJobsSTEM FuturesRole ProfilesmycareerpathProfessional Registration ApplicationsCSCS BackVotes & NominationsIExpE MerchandiseJournals2020 Journal Awards CompetitionPast PublicationsAbout The JournalAdvertising InformationJournal Subscription RatesSubmit An Article BackPublicationsPublications BackInstitute DocumentsIExpE Brand GuidelinesInstitute BusinessArticle of ConstitutionPolicy and ProceduresCode of ConductCPD PolicyPrivacy PolicyUseful Acronyms BackPartners & AffiliatesPartnersEU ExcertEU Excert UKEU ExImp ProjectSSB BackAffiliated OrganisationsSAFEXEFEEEngineering Council BackOrganisations of InterestCogentHSEEIFNational Occupational StandardsENBCBI Explosives Group Back BackIExpE PresidentIExpE Company Members BackNews & EventsInstitute NewsIExpE Conference CentreEventsFulmination 2021 Back
